Josuke, just how much
longer are you planning on playing?
If you don't turn it off
right this second,
I'm really gonna lose it.
Five more minutes! Please!
Just five more minutes!
The best part is coming up!
If I stop now,
I'll live the rest of my life
a man who can't follow through.
- It'll haunt me till the day I die!
- Okay! The longer you keep playing,
- Is that the kind of son you want, Mom?!
- the harder these kicks are gonna get!
Just how long can you hold out?
That's it…
Shii…
Put it away and
start your homework.
Jesus, you could at least take off
your uniform when you get home.
It's pitch-black out there!
I can't see you anymore.
Why, Sachiko?
You've stopped loving me?
- What the…?
- That's not it.
- I know I turned it off.
- I think I'm gonna leave town.
- Huh? Thing won't work.
- So you're just going to forget about me?
Looks like Jotaro Kujo has
refused to high-tail it out of this town…
And after I went through
all that trouble to warn him.
So, what gives,
Josuke Higashikata?
You're…
Chili Pepper?!
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
These faceless gazes pass by one another
A wound to the heart changes our everyday
Encounters without boundaries
The bizarre is our normal U-yeh
These ordinary mornings,
we're laughing on the surface
Mysteries drawn to each other,
identity still unknown
Without a heads up,
it's quietly lurking somewhere in this town
Although we bicker and complain
In the end, we celebrate
Dancing through the everyday
Crazy Noisy Bizarre Town
EPISODE 11
CHILI PEPPER, PART 1
What are you doing here?
Missed the boat again, I see.
I've been popping in
off and on for a while now.
What?
So this asshole's been
watching me this entire time!
The house belonging to the brother of
that fool, Keicho, I knocked off,
Okuyasu has been on
my "places to visit" list, too.
I'm also well aware of Yukako Yamagishi
and Koichi Hirose's Reverb.
And I know that Toshikazu Hazamada
and Tamami Kobayashi
are currently hospitalized.
That's why I'm asking.
What is a yellow,
sneaking coward like you
suddenly showing himself
fair and square to a guy like me?
You wouldn't…
be moronic enough to think you could
actually mess me up, would you?
Mess you up?
I'd never put you through
something so unpleasant.
I'm here to administer you
a humane death.
So you're a comedian with
a crappy sense of humor,
I see, sir.
I've told Jotaro myself.
His Star Platinum poses
a great threat to me.
His watchfulness is unwavering,
and Star Platinum's time-stopping ability
is formidable.
As you could guess, I was eager to see
how far my own Stand had evolved.
So, before I fought Jotaro,
I wanted to test my abilities
against you, Josuke Higashikata.
Why don't you come a little bit closer?
Closer!
I want you to be able
to unleash an attack
as speedy and precise
as Star Platinum, Josuke!
Come on! From back there,
your punches won't be quite up to snuff.
Am I detecting mockery?
Not in the slightest.
I just have a firm grasp on
your true capabilities.
Come closer and
give me your best shot.
Here!
Hit me right here, come on!
Scooch on in close.
Huh? H-He's fast…
I'm getting a little tired
of your squawking!
He's faster than I ever imagined!
Keep it up,
and I'll just have to
debeak you myself!
And by the way!
Jotaro's Star Platinum's got
nothing on me!
That was a mistake.
My arrogance got the best of me.
I underestimated his ability.
What?!
Josuke! What's with
all the commotion?
That blow…
That was like being on
the receiving end of a jet-engine blast…
He might be stronger than Mr. Jotaro…
Impressive, Josuke.
Your Shining Diamond is a surprise.
I guess I'm not the only one
who's matured.
It isn't my time yet.
Until Chili Pepper is stronger,
vanquishing Jotaro will remain
an impossibiltiy.
All he needs is
a source of electricity…
He has more than immense strength.
He can control his Stand from faraway.
Josuke, I asked you
what's with all the commotion!
It's nothing.
Dammit, another bug got me!
Son of a…
These things always swarm to me.
Ah, Josuke!
Sorry for the wait.
What is all this about, Josuke?
Why'd you want to meet
out here in the boondocks?
Couldn't we've gone to Tonio's
or that café?
I wasn't the one who called
you guys out here.
It was Jotaro.
Jotaro? Wonder what he wants.
I'm guessing it's about Chili Pepper.
What?! Chili Pepper?
You mean the Stand, Chili Pepper?!
So he's back…
Yeah. He came to my house last night.
You prick!
Why didn't you tell me right away?
Okuyasu…
He turns into a different person
at the slightest mention of Chili Pepper.
How can you blame him?
He lost his brother to that Stand…
I told Josuke to keep quiet.
Discussing this downtown
surrounded by electricity is too risky.
Jotaro!
I had us meet here
to avoid being overheard.
Okuyasu, you should know Chili Pepper
grates the shit outta me, too.
He slithers into people's homes.
He eavesdrops on conversations,
and swipes whatever he wants.
So that's why I woke up
to my homework
being gone from my desk the other day!
I could've sworn my mom
threw it out with the trash—
That's the least of our worries, Koichi!
What I'm saying is the only reason
Chili Pepper hasn't raised even
more hell is 'cause we're around.
With the ease of a dirty pervert
making an intrusive phone call,
he drags anyone who
pisses him off into the phone lines.
No doubt he has use
of the bow and arrow.
Question is who he's shot.
I know first-hand he's stronger now.
We have to find his user fast!
B-But how?
We're here together to
figure that out, right, Mr. Jotaro?
No, not quite.
Believe me, we will track him down.
And the one who's fit for the job
is arriving at
the Port of Morioh at noon today.
Huh?
You know someone who can find him?
Is he a Stand user?!
Uh-huh.
His Stand's is called Hermit Purple.
But he's way too old now.
Fighting's out of the question.
Too old? So how old is this guy?
So you've met this guy before?
Yeah. I know him well.
He used to be quite the beefcake,
though you wouldn't know it today.
He's 80… Or was it 79…
79?! He's ancient history!
His legs definitely aren't what
they used to be, so he's got a cane.
And two years ago
he had gallstones removed,
not to mention he had cataracts, too.
He has nothing but false teeth,
and grumbles about
missing his T-bone steaks.
He's also going senile.
Hey, come on.
Now you're gonna tell me
he likes talking to mailboxes.
Give me a break!
I had you guys come here
so you could protect the Old Man.
If Chili Pepper finds out he's here,
you can bet he'll take him down.
Because the thing Chili Pepper dreads
most is having his user identified.
Yeah, but how is an
old timer like that gonna help us?
I tried to stop him, but as soon as
he heard about the bow and arrow,
he headed to Japan on his own.
To Japan?
Mr. Jotaro, so this fellow isn't Japanese?
Correct.
Josuke, th-this is serious!
Huh? What is?
Josuke! Think about it…
A 79-year-old Stand user not from Japan…
Y-You can't mean…
I heard all I need to hear.
Chili Pepper!
Shit! How'd he get out here?
MORIOH LANDMARK #4
MORIOH GRAND HOTEL
HOW TO GET THERE: FROM TERMINAL #1,
TAKE THE "MORIOH GRAND
SWIMMING AREA" BUS
TO "MORIOH GRAND HOTEL".
SURROUNDED BY EXTRAVAGANT VILLAS,
THE MORIOH GRAND HOTEL OOZES
ELEGANCE AND OLD-WORLD CHARM,
AND FOR YEARS HAS BEEN
THE BELOVED GO-TO SPOT
FOR TRAVELERS TO MORIOH.
BESIDES ITS ACCOMMODATIONS,
THE HOTEL IS KNOWN FOR SERVING
MORIOH BEEF TONGUE TO CROWDS
OF ADORING REGULARS
AND TRAVELERS ALIKE.
Why?! There aren't any
power lines here, so how?!
The motorcycle battery.
Shit! He must've hidden in
the battery and followed us here.
In my motorcycle?
He heard us!
So, the port at noon, eh?
There's an old fogy
Stand user who can find me, huh?
The moment that codger
pulls into port, I'll massacre him!
Now he knows about the old man…
He knows…
about Josuke's father!
This isn't good.
At this rate, he's gonna get
to the old man before we do.
Josuke! We've got to chuck a rock
at that bike and take it down!
Not so fast.
In the name of revenge,
I, Okuyasu Nijimura,
will crush that criminal!
He cut through space!
Ack! Keicho's little brother!
You will fight me now.
I'll scratch you out!
Okuyasu, you have my compliments.
Teleporting yourself here
to the motorcycle was extraordinary.
But that little scratching motion
you do with The Hand
is no match for Chili Pepper's speed.
You're slow!
Take another look, dickhead.
When I said scratch you out,
I meant the motorcycle.
The front wheel!
You won't be escaping anywhere now.
Now that's using your head,
Okuyasu. Bravo!
Chili Pepper can't move
very far from the motocycle battery.
In other words… Look!
The nearest power line is
at least a hundred meters away.
We've got you bagged!
That was close!
We haven't captured him just yet.
The battery's still there.
He'll do whatever it
takes to kill Okuyasu and run.
We're going, too!
- Right!
You really think you've cornered me?
This is all to avenge Keicho, eh?
No.
My Bro…
his death was inevitable.
I knew someone would kill him one day.
The thing about crime is…
eventually, after a while,
in someway or another,
it all catches up with you.
That much even I know.
Now about your user…
Tell me who he is
and where he lives,
and I'll spare you your life.
If I tell you,
you'll spare me my life?
You are surprisingly composed.
I was certain the hollow of
your miserable bowels
would have burned with
vengeful fury by now!
Deep down, I was hoping you
wouldn't give me the info on your user!
I'm itching to scrape you away,
you electrified shit head!
There he is.
But you want to scrape me away?
With that tragically slow right hand?
I don't know whether
I should laugh or yawn!
It's a tough choice!
You bastard!
I'll annihilate you!
I'll make sure you truly realize
just how pathetically
sluggish your Stand is!
Do you get it now? You're slow!
Okuyasu!
- Okuyasu!
- Shit!
Here comes Jotaro…
I can't stick around here for long.
What?! He's behind me?!
I may've missed,
but I still swiped away space,
all so I could teleport!
Forget about that?
Got ya!
You beak-nosed freak!
Looks like you're dragging a bit now.
Think you can slip by my next attack?
Look! Chili Pepper's
electric charge is fading!
He's getting weaker!
His Stand power must be running out!
Looks like this is Okuyasu's win!
Okuyasu!
The finishing blow can wait!
Let us get there first.
You've already won!
We've got to get him to tell us
where the bow and arrow are.
You're right…
I am getting weaker.
Your Stand may be pathetically slow,
but its power is downright chilling.
However…
You sure you don't want to
wipe me out for good?
How do you know I'm not pretending
to be frail…
- Okuyasu?
- What?!
Perhaps I'm luring Jotaro
in close to quickly sheer off his head.
What is all this bullshit about?
Oh, nothing.
So what'll it be?
Will you kill me now,
or wait for Jotaro?
You bastard…
Wait a minute.
Why would you tell me all this?
If he hadn't hinted he was acting,
he could've easily played us all,
and taken me and Jotaro out…
Then that means, then…
Since he basically told me he's fine,
then my chance of him
attacking me is zero, right?
So I guess you want me
to kill you, after all!
I'll let you figure that out.
Could he really be at death's door?
Or was it all a lie,
and he's really fine?
Which could it be?
Are you going to do it or aren't you?
If he's not injured,
I have to kill him now.
He could have something up
his sleeve.
Should I?
Okuyasu… Something's wrong.
Make up your mind, Okuyasu.
Dammit!
The hell with everything, goddammit!
Okuyasu!
Don't even think
of stopping me, Jotaro!
He killed Bro!
And I'm gonna finish this!
There's only one truth…
And my heart doesn't lie!
Eat shit and die, shithole!
Well, that's great.
Finding the bow and arrow's
gonna be a real pain now.
So it's settled.
No, something's wrong.
It looks like Chili Pepper
really was plotting something.
Huh?!
Underground electrical cables?
That bastard!
He did all this so I'd expose them!
I really was fading.
That motorcycle battery holds
only 12 volts.
- Goodness, that was close!
- Why, you…
And you were considerate enough
to revive me!
Okuyasu!
If only you'd been a good boy
and controlled yourself
like Jotaro instructed,
I would've faded away
with the battery.
Wha…
I know the location of every
electrical line in this town.
I thought about escaping
into those cables,
but they were too far
from that motorcycle.
And there was no way I had
the strength to dig to the cables.
You bastard!
Now he's even more…
Which means that electricity,
that power…
is now my right hand.
Okuyasu!
I remember your brother Keicho
said you never failed to hold him back.
Now I know he was right.
Your soul is undeveloped.
Revenge was never
in the cards for you, idiot!
Bye-bye, Jotaro, Josuke!
And Joseph Joestar, was it?
I'll make sure that old coot will share
the same fate as the Nijimura Brothers!
I win!
Okuyasu!
He pulled him in!
Good grief.
To think we were that close,
and he still got away.
That was a pretty scary Stand.
Who'd a thunk: a remote Stand with
the boundless power to tap
- every electrical company within reach.
- What?! What are you guys saying?!
Okuyasu has just been murdered,
and you guys are talking about
how strong the enemy was?!
I suppose you're right.
Guess we should check up on Okuyasu.
Right.
There is one consolation.
Okuyasu must have a guardian angel.
Okuyasu was lucky
his right arm was chopped off.
Huh?
Shining Diamond!
Once I fix his arm,
his body will come back.
Damn it!
Yay! Okuyasu is back!
Shit… I-I…
I was totally outclassed
by that bastard.
Dammit! Dammit!
It's not about getting revenge
or winning or losing.
We have to think about
protecting Joseph Joestar.
That's how we'll defeat Chili Pepper.
You have to… for everyone.
For our town…
Jotaro, this really isn't good.
I guess I took it all too lightly.
Yeah. We have to reach the old
man's boat before Chili Pepper.
We can head to the port now.
Hey, you guys!
How could you be so nonchalant?
Okuyasu's still in shock!
It's faster to the port this way.
All right.
Hey, wait!
I've got to surpass my Bro…
I learned a lot from this,
Chili Pepper.
Mr. Joestar.
We'll be arriving at
the Port of Morioh any moment now.
EPISODE 12
CHILI PEPPER, PART 2